이런! 미안, 미안!
-I'm sorry!
-That is it!
세상에, 노크도 안하고
그냥 들어온 거야?
You barge in here
and you don't knock?
- 미안해
- 사생활 보호란 말도 몰라?
You have no respect for privacy.
No, you wait!
- 그건 아냐
- 이런 법이 어딨어?
- 나도 말 좀 하자
- 뭔데?
-Can I just say one thing?
-What?!
That's a relatively open weave.
I can still see...
지금 너무 방심해서...
못 볼 걸 본 것 같은데
...your nippular areas.
The One With The Boobies
Honey, tell them the story
about your patient...
자기야!
자기 환자들의 기상천외한
사건 좀 말해 봐
...who thinks things are
other things.
있잖아?
샤워하면서 전화하는
여자 말이야
When the phone rings
and she takes a shower.
너무 개인적인 얘긴데
That's pretty much it.
-But you tell it really well, sweetie.
-Thanks. Okay.
자기가 대신 얘기해도 돼
알았어
우리끼리 얘기 좀 할게
Now go away so we can
talk about you.
빨리 끝내
Okay. I'll miss you.
정말 멋있지?
-lsn't he great?
-He's cute. He likes you so much.
보기 좋다!
널 많이 좋아하나 봐
그런 거 같애
다정하고도 복잡한 사람이야
I know. He's so sweet.
And so complicated, you know?
그래도 정신과 의사치고는
많이 안 복잡해
And for a shrink,
he's not too shrinky.
Think you'll do it on his couch?
저 남자 병원에서
데이트하고 싶니?
I don't know. That's a little weird.
아니, 모르겠어
그건 좀 이상하지?
It's vinyl.
난 환자 아니잖아
마실 거 필요해?
Okay, you guys want anything else?
- 응, 나는...
- 다 떨어졌어
-Could I have?
-We're all out. Anybody else?
- 다른 거 주문해
- 알았어
Did I miss something?
왜 저러는 거야?
내가 자기 가슴을 봤다고
예민해있어
No, she's still upset
because I saw her boobies.
어떻게 가슴을 봤는데?
What were you doing
seeing her boobies?
It was an accident. I wasn't
across the street with a telescope.
우연이었어
뭐 먹을 거 있나
보러 갔다가 그렇게 됐어
제발, 화제 좀 바꿀래?
Can we change the subject, please?
그냥 가슴이야
여자라고 생각하지마
These aren't her "boobies."
These are her breasts.
Pheebs, I was hoping
for more of a change.
피비, 화제 좀 바꾸자
I always liked "Bazoombas."
난 '바줌바 브라'가 좋아
라틴어처럼 들리잖아
Gives them a Latin spin.
제발 그만 할 수 없니?
Can we drop this already, please?
그렇게 창피해할 필요 없어
그냥 예쁜 가슴이었어
Why are you embarrassed?
They were very nice boobies.
"Nice"? They were "nice"?
예쁜?
예뻤다구?
남의 가슴을 그렇게 표현해?
That's it?
I mean, mittens are "nice."
알았어
샤워, 가슴, 그리고 나
Okay. Rock, hard place. Me.
You're so funny!
되게 웃긴다
정말 웃기는군
He's really funny.
대단한 유머 감각이야
I wouldn't wanna be there
when the laughter stops.
Whoa, back up there, sparky.
내 편들어줘서 고마워요
What did you mean by that?
그런데 무슨 뜻이죠?
It seems that maybe
you have intimacy issues...
그건 아주 친한 사이에서만
할 수 있는 말인데
그런 농담은 대인관계가
불편하단 뜻이죠
...that you use your humor
to keep people at a distance.
당신을 오늘 만나서
잘 몰라도...
I mean, I just met you.
I don't know you from Adam.
그래도 유치하네요
Only child, right?
사춘기 전에
부모가 이혼했죠?
Parents divorced
before you hit puberty.
어떻게 알았어요?
-How did you know that?
-It's textbook.
티가 나요
Hey, you guys.
You all know my dad, right?
여기들 있구나!
아버지 오셨어
-How long are you in the city?
-Two days. I got a job.
오래 계실거죠?
한 이틀 있을 건데
시내에 볼일이 있어
I'm better off staying with Joey...
얘 고모보다는 내가
오는 게 낫지
...than going back and forth
on the ferry.
이 친구는 누구지?
-I don't know this one.
-This is my friend Roger.
제 친구 로저예요
- 안녕하세요?
- 반갑네, 로저
-Good to meet you.
-You too.
-What happened to the puppet guy?
-Dad.
인형극 한다는
친구는 쫑났니?
아버지...
Oh, excuse me.
So, Ross, how's the wife?
아! 미안해
로스, 아내는 잘 있나?
0 for 2, huh?
아니 둘이었나?
Chandler, say something funny.
챈들러, 농담 좀 해봐
금방 갈게
I gotta go. Miss you too.
나도 보고 싶어, 사랑해
지금은 늦었어...
-I love you, but it's getting late
-Say hi. Hey, Ma.
바꿔주세요
엄마!
병원에 예약했어요...
I made the appointment
with Dr. Bassida and
Excuse me?
누구시죠?
이 여자 아세요?
Did you know this isn't Ma?
이름은 로니야
Her name's Ronni.
She's a pet mortician.
동물 장의사지
Sure.
So, how long you been...?
만난 지 얼마나...
네가 꼬마였을 때
해군 부대에 갔던 거 기억하니?
Remember when you were a kid,
I'd take you to the navy yard?
그때부터예요?
-Since then?
-No, it's only been six years.
아니, 6년 됐다
I wanted you to think of a nice memory
so you'd know I'm not a terrible guy.
너에게 좋은 추억을 만들어준
좋은 아빠로 남고 싶었단다
-What are you doing?
-Chopping garlic.
뭐 하는 거냐?
- 마늘 찧어요
- 다 갈아 버릴 거니?
You don't crush it?
아빠는 바람피우고
아들은 마늘 찧고
You're having an affair,
I chop garlic. It's a wacky world.
세상 좋죠?
너 사랑해본 적 있니?
Joe, you ever been in love?
-I don't know.
-Then you haven't.
모르겠어요
그럼 모르겠구나
젊음을 헛되이 하지 마라
-You're burning tomatoes.
-You're one to talk.
그냥 말씀하세요
네 아빠가 사랑에 빠진 거야
문제는, 여자가 둘이라는 거지
Your dad's in love. The worst part is,
it's with two different women.
세상에!
Oh, man! Please tell me
one of them is Ma.
둘 중에 한 명은 엄마죠?
당연히 네 엄마지
너 지금 제정신이냐?
Of course one of them's Ma.
What's the matter with you?
갑자기, 너희 아버지가
이중생활을 한다고 생각해봐
It's like if you woke up
and found out...
...your dad leads this double life.
He's like actually some spy
working for the ClA.
아빠가 CIA에 소속된
간첩이라고 생각해 보라구
That'd be cool.
차라리 그게 낫지
이건 뻥이야!
This blows!
- 우리 아빠도 바람 핀 적 있을까?
- 아니길 바래
Do you think Dad cheated?
I don't think so.
That would involve sex.
이건 섹스에 관한 얘긴데
부모님과 연관짓기 싫어
I'd like to think that our parents
don't do that.
I know. Why can't parents
just stay parents?
이해해, 부모님은
다를 거라도 생각하지
그분들도 인간이야
그러니까 당연히...
Why do they have to become people?
Why do they have?
근데...
Why...
내 가슴 좀 그만 볼래?
...can't you stop staring
at my breasts?
What?
뭐?
Didn't you get a good enough look?
전에 본 걸로 충분치 않아?
그래, 그만 해
우린 성인이야
We're all adults here.
There's only one way to resolve this.
방법은 하나뿐이다
Since you saw her boobies you have
to show her your pee-pee.
네가 레이첼 가슴을 봤으니까
넌 네 거를 보여줘
나도 본지가 꽤 됐어
You know,
I don't see that happening.
Come on. He's right. Tit for tat.
로스 말이 맞아
'이에는 이'
Well, I'm not showing you my tat!
내 이빨 다 보고싶어?
누구세요?
-It's Phoebe.
-And Rog!
- 피비야
- 로저도
Come on up.
올라와
이런! 로저가 왔군
Oh, good! Rog is here.
로저 만나기 싫어?
-What's the matter with Rog?
-It's a little thing. I hate that guy!
아냐, 그냥
솔직히, 그 자식 싫어
분석적이라서?
직업이 그렇잖아
So he was a little analytical.
That's what he does.
그렇게 싫어할 거 없어
Come on, he's not that bad.
그게 틀린 거야
You're wrong! Why would I marry her...
내가 왜 레즈비언과
결혼을 감행했겠어?
...if I thought that she was
a lesbian?
그거야 모르지
이혼을 원했던 거 아냐?
I don't know. Maybe you wanted
your marriage to fail.
Why? Why would l? Why?
왜? 왜 내가 이혼을?
왜? 왜 원해?
I don't know. Maybe low self-esteem?
몰라, 아마...
자신감이 없었든지...
Maybe to compensate
for overshadowing a sibling. Maybe
형제에 대한
보상심리라든지...
잠깐!
형제가 뭐 어째?
Wait! Go back to that "sibling" thing.
뭐? 나도 몰라
Well, I don't know.
형제의 실패를 덮어주기 위해서
결혼을 망치고 싶었겠지
You could've sabotaged
your marriage...
...so the sibling would feel like
less of a failure.
That's ridiculous!
I don't feel guilty for her failures.
그건 말도 안돼!
동생의 실패에
내가 왜 책임을 느껴?
-You think I'm a failure?
-lsn't he good?
그럼 내가 실패자야?
- 멋지지 않니?
- 그래
Yeah. No, that's not
what I was saying.
아니
내 말의 의미를 알지?
난 오빠가 내 편인줄 알았는데
I thought you were on my side.
But maybe you sucked up
to them so they'd favor you.
이제 보니까 그저 부모님
생각뿐이었구나?
I married a lesbian
to make you look good!
너한테 잘 보이려고
레즈비언과 결혼했었다
그 말이 맞아, 정말 맞아
You're right. I mean, you're right.
It wasn't just the Weebles,
but the Weeble Play Palace...
그냥 사소한 일이지
하지만 그 사소함이 뭉치면...
...and the Weeble's Cruise Ship...
커져서 커다란 짐이 돼
그런 사소함 속에 묻혀
허우적대는 게 인간이야
...with this lifeboat
for the Weebles to wobble in.
And Mom just gave them all away.
그건 너무 까다로운 문제야
That's tough, tough stuff.
피비, 가자
극장에 가야지
Pheebs, we're gonna catch that movie,
we gotta go.
레이첼, 다 잊어버려
-Feel better.
-We're gonna be late, sweetie.
- 우리 늦겠어
- 알았어
- 저녁 잘 먹었어, 모니카
- 됐어
-Thanks for everything, Mon.
-No problem.
다들, 또 만나길 바래
Listen, it was great seeing you again.
모니카
과자 너무 씹지마
Mon, easy on those cookies, okay?
그냥 음식이지
전 남편이 아냐
Remember, they're just food,
they're not love.
얄미워 죽겠어
I hate that guy!
잘 자
Good night, you guys.
네가 부른 여자니?
Oh, look. It's the woman we ordered.
무슨 일이신가요?
Hey, can we help you?
조이라는 청년을
만나러 왔어요
No, thanks. I'm just waiting
for Joey Tribbiani.
제가 조이입니다
I'm Joey Tribbiani.
그럴 리 없는데!
다 컸구나!
Oh, no, not you. Big Joey. Oh, my God!
사진보다 훨씬 잘 생겼네
You're so much cuter than
your pictures.
난 로니야!
I'm Ronni.
치즈 과자 먹을래?
Cheese Nip?
얘는 치즈 알레르기가
있어요
Joey's having an embolism,
but I'd go for a nip.
제가 대신 먹죠
Most people,
when their pets pass on...
사람들은 애완동물이 죽으면
자는 모습으로 장례를 치르지만
...want them like they're sleeping.
가끔, 어떤 사람들은
포즈를 잡아주길 원해
Occasionally you get a person
who wants them in a pose.
꼬리를 쫓는 모습이나...
Like chasing their tail.
공 받는 모습 같은 거
Or jumping to catch a Frisbee.
나 죽으면, 열쇠 찾는 모습으로
만들어 줄래?
Joey, if I go first,
I wanna be looking for my keys.
그거 좋네
-That's a good one!
-Hey.
- 조이!
- 아빠!
Hey, Dad. Ronni's here.
- 아줌마 왔어요
- 뭐?
-Hi.
-Hey.
- 안녕!
- 나 왔어
- 안녕, 자기
Hello, babe! What are you doing here?
여긴 어쩐 일이야?
당신이 가발을 놓고 갔어
내일 꼭 필요한 거지?
Oh, you left your hair at my place.
I thought you'd need it tomorrow.
고마워
Thank you.
저랑 게임 하실 분,
손들어 봐요
So, who's up for a big
game of Kerplunk?
내가... 괜히 왔나봐
Look, I shouldn't have come.
그만 가볼게
기차 시간이 다 됐어
I better go. I'll miss the train.
안돼! 이렇게 늦은 시간에
나가면 위험해
-I don't want you taking that thing.
-Where do I stay? Here?
그럼 여기 있으라구?
We'll go to a hotel.
호텔로 가지
호텔로 가
- 안 돼요
- 안 된대
-No, you won't.
-No, we won't.
호텔에 가시면 일이 커져요
If you go to a hotel,
you'll be doing stuff.
그냥 여기 계세요
잘 감시하게요
I want you here so I can
keep an eye on you.
-You're gonna keep an eye on us?
-Right.
- 우릴 감시하겠다구?
- 네, 맞습니다!
아버지가 몇 살이든, 제 집에
있는 한 제 규칙을 따라주세요
As long as you are under my roof...
...you're gonna live by my rules.
그 뜻은 여자친구와
함께 못 잔다는 말이죠
That means no sleeping
with your girlfriend.
엄한 아드님이네!
Wow, he's strict.
아버지는 제 방으로!
아주머니는 챈들러 방으로!
Dad, you'll be in my room.
You can stay in Chandler's room.
그럼 챈들러는?
And Chandler will be?
- 우린 거실 소파에서 자자
- 대충 자자?
Out here with me, bunking up.
Oh, bunking up. If you smell s'mores,
don't be alarmed.
거실에서 어떤 소리가 나도
깨지 마세요
Thanks. You're a good kid.
고맙다, 넌...
착한 애야
제 방으로 안내해 드릴게요
I'll show you to my room.
이 집 규칙 중에, '밤늦게
손님 안 받는다'는 없냐?
That sounds weird not followed by,
"No, it's late."
This is just for tonight.
Tomorrow you gotta change.
오늘뿐이에요
내일부터 모두 바꾸세요
6년이면 너무 길어요
뭘 바꿔?
Change?
- 저 아줌마랑 헤어지던지...
- 그건 안돼
-Break up with Ronni
-I can't!
그럼 엄마한테 고백하세요!
이건 안 돼요
Then come clean with Ma!
This is not right!
나도 알지만...
변명은 필요 없어요
방으로 가세요!
I don't wanna hear it!
Now go to my room!
Hey, kickie!
야, 체조해?
-What are you doing?
-Getting comfortable.
왜 그러는 거야?
불편해서 그래
원래 팬티 입고 못 자
-I can't sleep in my underwear.
-Well, you're gonna.
그래도 벗지마
I was thinking about how I'm always
seeing girls on top of girls....
생각해 봤는데...
나는 늘 여자 생각뿐이잖아
Are they end-to-end,
or tall, like pancakes?
그 생각... 시간대냐?
아님 사건별이냐?
You know, how I date all these women.
내가 여자들을 어떤 식으로
만났는지 네가 알잖아
그러다, 언젠가 운명을 만나면
그녀만 보고 살 거라고 생각했어
I always figured, when the right one
comes along...
... I'll be able to go the distance.
그런데 어버지를 보니까...
Now I'm looking at my dad, thinking
너와 아버지는 달라
넌 너야!
You're not him, you're you.
사람들이 아버지의 배관 일을
이어받으라고 했을 때, 했어?
When they wanted you in
your father's business, did you cave?
- 아니
- 아니지?
-No.
넌 배우 일을 택했어
You chose
the out-of-work-actor business.
That wasn't easy, but you did it.
쉽지 않았는데, 거부했잖아
I believe when the right woman
comes along...
그러니까 인연을 만나 결혼하면
여자에게 이럴 거야
...you'll have the guts to say,
"No, thanks, I'm married."
난 유부남이오
-You really think so?
-Yeah, I really do.
정말 그럴까?
응, 진짜야
-Thanks, Chandler.
-Get off!
- 고마워, 챈들러
- 저리 가
- 안녕
- 안녕하세요?
-Hi.
-Hi. May I help you?
무슨 일이죠?
조이가 여기서 샤워를 하래
챈들러가 욕실에 있거든
Joey said I could use your shower
since Chandler's in ours.
그런데, 누구시죠?
Okay. Who are you?
Oh, I'm Ronni. Ronni Rapalono.
난 로니야, 로니 라팔로노
그 분 애인!
The mistress?
- 들어오세요
- 고맙다
-Come on in.
-Thanks.
- 저는 레이첼이에요
- 안녕!
I'm Rachel. Bathroom's there.
- 욕실은 위에 있어요
- 그래
Ronni, how long has Chandler
been in the shower?
챈들러가 욕실에 들어간지
얼마나 됐어요?
Oh, like five minutes.
- 한 5분쯤
- 알았어요
Perfect.
Fasten your seat belts,
it's pee-pee time.
챈들러, 꼼짝 마
이제 네 차례야
-Hey, Mr. Trib.
-Hey, good morning, dear.
- 안녕하세요, 아저씨
- 잘 잤니?
Chandler Bing,
it's time to see your thing.
챈들러!
네 거 보여줄 시간이야
-What's with you?
-I thought it was Chandler!
- 너 왜 그래?
- 챈들러가 있는 줄 알았어
뭐야?
네 걸 봐야한다는 생각에
욕실 문을 열어버렸어
You were supposed to be in there
so I'd see your thing!
Sorry, my thing was in there with me.
안됐다
내 거는 이 방에 있었어
- 안녕
- 피비!
- 어서 와
-How's it going?
-Good.
- 어때?
- 좋아
Roger's having a dinner thing.
He wanted me to invite you guys.
로저가 너희들을 저녁식사에
초대하고 싶대
-So, what's going on?
-Nothing.
- 왜들 그래?
- 아냐
It's just....
그게...
It's Roger, you know?
- 로저 때문이야
- 그래?
잘은 모르지만...
There's something about
We just feel that he's....
근본적으로 우리의 생각은...
-We hate that guy!
-We hate him!
- 우린 로저가 싫어
- 정말 싫어!
-We're sorry, Pheebs.
-Okay.
- 미안해, 피비
- 알았어
너희들을 놀라게 한
그 예민한 지각 때문이니?
Don't you think it's just that
he's so perceptive...
...it freaked you out?
No, we hate him!
- 아니, 난 그냥 싫어
- 그냥 싫어
미안해
I'm sorry.
-Ma! What are you doing here?
-I came to give you this and this!
엄마!
웬일이세요?
이거 주러 왔고...
이것도!
아파요
Big ring!
Why'd you fill your father's head
with garbage...
왜 아빠 마음 속에 도덕적
양심을 느끼게 만들었니?
...about making things right?
지금까지 모든 게 좋았어
Things were fine this way!
There's chicken in there. Put it away.
그거 닭고기니까
냉장고에 넣어
세상에, 조이...
For God's sake, Joey! Really.
그럼, 아셨어요?
-Hold on. You knew?
-Of course I knew. What do you think?
당연히 알지
무슨 소리냐?
네 아빠는 간첩이 아니야
누구나 알도록 하고 다니니까
Your father is no James Bond.
You should've heard his stories.
'난 지금 바람피워요'하고 표시나
그게 어때서?
"I'm sleeping over
at my accountant's."
-What is that? Please!
-So then, how could you?
그럼...
어떻게 엄마는...
네 아빠가 어땠는지
기억나니?
Do you remember
how your father used to be?
맨날 소리만 질렀어, 소리만
뭐든지 불만이었어, 뭐든지
Always yelling.
Nothing made him happy.
Not that wood shop, not those
stupid little ships in the bottle.
목재상도, 모형 배 만들기도
즐겁지가 않았다
그런데 이젠 행복하셔
잘된 일이야
Now he's happy. I mean, it's nice.
He has a hobby.
취미가 생겼잖니?
무례한 소리인지 모르지만...
Ma, I don't mean
to be disrespectful...
... but what the hell
are you talking about?
대체 이게 말이 돼요?
-I mean, what about you?
-Me? I'm fine.
- 그럼 엄마는요?
- 나?
난 괜찮아
상상의 세계에서
나는 영화배우랑 살아
Look, honey, in an ideal world...
...there'd be no her and your father
would look like Sting.
애완동물 만진다는 그 여자를
만난 이후로는...
And something else:
Ever since that
poodle-stuffer came along...
... he's so ashamed of himself
that he's been more attentive.
네 아빠가 다정하고
사랑스러워졌단다
He's been more loving. It's like
every day is our anniversary.
매일 매일 기념일 같아
-I'm happy for you?
-Well, don't be!
- 축하해 드려요?
- 아니!
이제 모든 게 탄로 났으니까
다시 제자리로 돌려놔야지
Now everything's screwed up.
I just want it the way it was.
죄송해요
엄마를 생각해서 그런 거였어요
Ma, I'm sorry.
I just did what
I thought you'd want.
I know you did, cookie.
I know you did.
다 알아, 녀석아
알고 있어
So tell me. Did you see her?
말해줄래?
그 여자 봤니?
네
Yeah.
-You're 10 times prettier than she is.
-That's sweet.
엄마가 10배는 더 예뻐요
고맙다
진짜 이길 수 있을까?
Could I take her?
With this ring, no contest.
이만한 반지라면
상대가 안 되죠
안돼, 이러지 마
Oh, no! Don't ever do that!
- 왜?
- 미안해, 정말
-What?
-I'm sorry.
I have a thing,
which means you can't ever do that!
난 원래 싫어해
절대로 하지마
- 무슨 일 있어?
- 아니, 없어
-What's wrong, sweetie?
-Nothing.
아니, 무슨 일이야?
-No, what's wrong? Come on.
-Okay.
알았어
별일 아니야, 난 괜찮아
It's nothing. I'm fine.
It's just It's my friends.
그게... 친구들 문제야
당신에 대한 선호도에
문제가 생겼어
They have a liking problem with you...
...in that they don't.
당신이 싫대
그래... 싫대?
They don't?
친구들은 내가 아는 당신의
장점을 아직 못 봐서 그래
But they don't see all
the wonderfulness that I see.
당신의 좋은 면과
다정한 면을 못 봤어
They don't see all the good
and sweet stuff.
애들은 당신이 좀...
-They think you're a little
-What?
뭔데?
예민해서 소름끼친대
Intense and creepy.
-Oh.
-But I don't. Me, Phoebe.
난 안 그래
나! 피비
그렇게 생각할 줄 알았어
-I'm not at all surprised about that.
-That's why you're so great.
그랬어?
당신 정말 대단해
솔직히 비정상적인 친구들의
전형적인 행동방식이 그래
It's quite typical behavior...
...when you have this kind
of dysfunctional group dynamic.
서로에게 종속되어서
감정적으로 쫀쫀해지고...
You know, this kind of codependent,
emotionally stunted...
이런 촌스런 카페에 모여서
커다란 컵에 커피나 마시고
...sitting in your stupid coffeehouse,
with your stupid big cups...
가슴 얘기나 해대면서...
...which might as well
have nipples on them.
이렇게 말하지
And you're all like,
"Oh, define me! Define me!
"내가 뭘까, 내 존재가 뭘까?
사랑해 줘, 난 사랑이 필요해"
Love me! I need love!
You talked to your dad?
아빠랑 얘기 좀 해봤어?
He's gonna keep cheating on Ma
like she wanted.
엄마가 원하는 대로
계속 바람을 피우시겠대
엄마는 다 알면서도
계속 모른 척 하실 거고
Ma will keep pretending
she doesn't know.
여동생 티나는 접근금지
명령 때문에 남편을 못 만난대
And my sister, Tina,
can't see her husband.
He got a restraining order.
부모님 일과는 아무 상관도
없는 얘기지만
Which has nothing to do with it.
I found out today.
Things have changed here
on Waltons'mountain.
우리 인생이 다 그런 거 아냐?
-So, Joey, are you okay?
-Yeah, I guess.
조이, 넌 괜찮아?
그런 거 같아
It's just You know, they're parents.
부모란 어떤 시점이 되면
손을 놔야 하는 거야
After a certain point,
you gotta let go.
You gotta let them
make their own mistakes.
누구나 그런 실수를 하면서
성숙해 지는 거지
생각해봐
And think, in a few years,
we'll turn into them.
몇 년 뒤엔
우리도 부모들처럼 될 거야
관둬라...
Oh, please.
꼭 그렇게 닮아간다면
차라리 게이가 되는 게 낫겠다
If I turn into my parents, I'll be
an alcoholic blond chasing men...
...or I'll end up like my mom!
아니면, 우리 엄마처럼 되잖아
- 안녕!
- 어서 와, 피비
-Hey.
-Hey, Pheebs.
일은 잘 되지?
How's it going?
응, 로저와 헤어진 것만 빼고
Okay, except I broke up with Roger.
-Yeah, right.
-No, no, really.
- 너희들이 옳았어
- 아니, 그게 아닌데...
-What happened?
-I don't know. I mean...
왜 그랬어?
나도 몰라
... he's a good person,
and he can be really sweet.
좋은 사람이고
참 다정한 사람이야
In some ways,
I think he is so right for me.
어떤 면에서 보면
나랑 천생연분이지
It's just.... I hate that guy!
그런데...
그 사람이 싫어!
어서 와!
무슨 일이야?
Hi, Joey. What's going on?
신체 엿보기 복수전이야
이번 차례는 레이첼 그린...
Clear the tracks
for the boobie payback.
Next stop, Rachel Greene.
이게 무슨 짓이야?
Joey, what the hell were you doing?
미안!
가슴이 바뀐 것 뿐이야
Sorry, wrong boobies!
안녕, 조이!
Hello, Joey!
안녕, 얘야
Hello, dear!